<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="zh"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="zh" /><updated>2023-09-03T19:42:49+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">当渐行渐远的风不再歌唱</title><subtitle>确实，我还在成长</subtitle><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><entry><title type="html">2023-07-15-Are Double Standards Hypocritical?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Are-Double-Standards-Hypocritical/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2023-07-15-Are Double Standards Hypocritical?" /><published>2023-07-15T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-15T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Are-Double-Standards-Hypocritical</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Are-Double-Standards-Hypocritical/">&lt;p&gt;​	A double standard is a situation where different rules or principles are applied to similar cases in an unfair way. For example, some people may judge men and women differently for having the same sexual behavior, or some employers may pay workers differently for doing the same job. Double standards are often seen as a form of hypocrisy, bias or injustice, but some people may argue that they are justified or inevitable in certain situations. In this article, we will present a summary of a debate on the topic “Are double standards hypocritical?”, where two contestants, A and B, expressed their views and arguments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	The debate followed a simple format and rules: each contestant had five minutes to present their position and three minutes to rebut their opponent’s position. The debate was judged by a panel of experts and an audience, who evaluated the content, logic, evidence and manner of the speakers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	Contestant A spoke first and argued that double standards are hypocritical. He defined hypocrisy as the act of pretending to have moral standards or beliefs that one does not actually have or follow. He gave some examples of double standards in society, such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Politicians who claim to be honest and transparent but are involved in corruption or scandals.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Religious leaders who preach about morality and virtue but commit sins or crimes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Celebrities who advocate for environmental causes but have lavish lifestyles that contribute to pollution or waste.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	He said that these examples show that double standards are dishonest, inconsistent and unfair. He said that double standards undermine trust, respect and equality in society. He said that people who use double standards are selfish, cowardly and irresponsible. He concluded by saying that double standards are hypocritical and should be avoided or exposed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	Contestant B spoke next and argued that double standards are not hypocritical. He defined hypocrisy as the act of deliberately deceiving others or oneself about one’s moral standards or beliefs. He gave some examples of situations where double standards are reasonable or necessary, such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Parents who have different expectations or rules for their children based on their age, gender or personality.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Teachers who have different methods or criteria for teaching or assessing their students based on their abilities, interests or needs.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Judges who have different sentences or punishments for offenders based on their circumstances, motives or remorse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	He said that these examples show that double standards are realistic, flexible and fair. He said that double standards reflect diversity, complexity and context in society. He said that people who use double standards are pragmatic, adaptable and compassionate. He concluded by saying that double standards are not hypocritical and should be accepted or understood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	After presenting their positions, each contestant had three minutes to rebut their opponent’s position. Contestant A challenged contestant B’s definition of hypocrisy and said that it was too narrow and subjective. He said that hypocrisy is not only about deliberate deception but also about unintentional contradiction or ignorance. He said that people who use double standards may not be aware of their own biases or inconsistencies, but they still harm themselves or others by doing so. He said that contestant B’s examples of reasonable or necessary double standards were actually cases of different standards rather than double standards. He said that different standards are applied to different cases based on objective facts or values rather than subjective preferences or prejudices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	Contestant B challenged contestant A’s definition of hypocrisy and said that it was too broad and vague. He said that hypocrisy is not only about contradiction or ignorance but also about intention or motivation. He said that people who use double standards may have good reasons or goals for doing so, but they still benefit themselves or others by doing so. He said that contestant A’s examples of hypocritical double standards were actually cases of personal opinions rather than universal truths. He said that personal opinions are influenced by culture, history and experience rather than logic, evidence or morality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	The debate ended with each contestant summarizing their main points and appealing to the judges and the audience. The judges and the audience then voted for the winner based on their own criteria and preferences.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html">​ A double standard is a situation where different rules or principles are applied to similar cases in an unfair way. For example, some people may judge men and women differently for having the same sexual behavior, or some employers may pay workers differently for doing the same job. Double standards are often seen as a form of hypocrisy, bias or injustice, but some people may argue that they are justified or inevitable in certain situations. In this article, we will present a summary of a debate on the topic “Are double standards hypocritical?”, where two contestants, A and B, expressed their views and arguments. ​ The debate followed a simple format and rules: each contestant had five minutes to present their position and three minutes to rebut their opponent’s position. The debate was judged by a panel of experts and an audience, who evaluated the content, logic, evidence and manner of the speakers. ​ Contestant A spoke first and argued that double standards are hypocritical. He defined hypocrisy as the act of pretending to have moral standards or beliefs that one does not actually have or follow. He gave some examples of double standards in society, such as: Politicians who claim to be honest and transparent but are involved in corruption or scandals. Religious leaders who preach about morality and virtue but commit sins or crimes. Celebrities who advocate for environmental causes but have lavish lifestyles that contribute to pollution or waste. ​ He said that these examples show that double standards are dishonest, inconsistent and unfair. He said that double standards undermine trust, respect and equality in society. He said that people who use double standards are selfish, cowardly and irresponsible. He concluded by saying that double standards are hypocritical and should be avoided or exposed. ​ Contestant B spoke next and argued that double standards are not hypocritical. He defined hypocrisy as the act of deliberately deceiving others or oneself about one’s moral standards or beliefs. He gave some examples of situations where double standards are reasonable or necessary, such as: Parents who have different expectations or rules for their children based on their age, gender or personality. Teachers who have different methods or criteria for teaching or assessing their students based on their abilities, interests or needs. Judges who have different sentences or punishments for offenders based on their circumstances, motives or remorse. ​ He said that these examples show that double standards are realistic, flexible and fair. He said that double standards reflect diversity, complexity and context in society. He said that people who use double standards are pragmatic, adaptable and compassionate. He concluded by saying that double standards are not hypocritical and should be accepted or understood. ​ After presenting their positions, each contestant had three minutes to rebut their opponent’s position. Contestant A challenged contestant B’s definition of hypocrisy and said that it was too narrow and subjective. He said that hypocrisy is not only about deliberate deception but also about unintentional contradiction or ignorance. He said that people who use double standards may not be aware of their own biases or inconsistencies, but they still harm themselves or others by doing so. He said that contestant B’s examples of reasonable or necessary double standards were actually cases of different standards rather than double standards. He said that different standards are applied to different cases based on objective facts or values rather than subjective preferences or prejudices. ​ Contestant B challenged contestant A’s definition of hypocrisy and said that it was too broad and vague. He said that hypocrisy is not only about contradiction or ignorance but also about intention or motivation. He said that people who use double standards may have good reasons or goals for doing so, but they still benefit themselves or others by doing so. He said that contestant A’s examples of hypocritical double standards were actually cases of personal opinions rather than universal truths. He said that personal opinions are influenced by culture, history and experience rather than logic, evidence or morality. ​ The debate ended with each contestant summarizing their main points and appealing to the judges and the audience. The judges and the audience then voted for the winner based on their own criteria and preferences.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Past and Future of Humanity</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/The-Past-and-Future-of-Humanity/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Past and Future of Humanity" /><published>2023-07-14T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-14T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/The-Past-and-Future-of-Humanity</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/The-Past-and-Future-of-Humanity/">&lt;p&gt;​	Human beings are one of the most intelligent and creative species on Earth, and their history and evolution have always been topics of interest for scientists. Where did humans come from? Where are humans going? These questions may never have definite answers, but we can speculate about the future of humanity by studying their past and present.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	According to scientific evidence, humans first appeared in Africa about 300,000 years ago, when they belonged to the species Homo sapiens. Homo sapiens are the only surviving species of the genus Homo, but not the first one. Before Homo sapiens, there were several other species of Homo, such as Homo erectus, Homo heidelbergensis and Homo neanderthalensis. These species are all extinct now, but they may have had genetic exchanges with Homo sapiens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	In the past few million years, humans have undergone many significant changes and adaptations to cope with different environments and challenges. For example, humans developed features such as upright walking, dexterous fingers and complex language. These features enabled humans to make tools, hunt food, build societies and cultures, and explore the mysteries of nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	So, what kind of changes will humans experience in the next few million years? This question is hard to answer, because the future is unpredictable and depends on many factors, such as natural selection, genetic mutation, environmental change, technological development, etc. However, some futurists have proposed some possibilities and scenarios that allow us to imagine what the future of humanity might look like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	One possibility is that humans will become smaller, thinner, paler and longer-lived. This might be because in a highly developed and crowded world, a small body can save energy and space, while a pale skin can absorb more vitamin D. Moreover, medical and genetic technology might also extend human lifespan and health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	Another possibility is that humans will become hybrid beings of half-mechanical and half-biological parts. This might be because in a highly competitive and complex world, humans need to rely on high-tech implants or replacements to enhance their abilities and adaptability. For example, humans might have mechanical eyes that can take photos, zoom in or see different frequencies of light; or mechanical limbs that can regenerate, transform or increase strength.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	Of course, these are just some speculations, not certain predictions. The future of humanity might have many different directions and possibilities, and it might also be affected by some unforeseeable events or disasters. Therefore, humans need to maintain an open and flexible attitude to deal with the uncertainty and change of the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	The past and future of humanity is a fascinating topic that can help us understand our origin and destiny, as well as stimulate our imagination and creativity. By reading this article, you might have learned more about the history and evolution of humanity, and you might also have more curiosity and expectation about the future of humanity. In any case, we should cherish our identity and traits as human beings, while also respecting and protecting the Earth and other living beings that we share it with.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html">​ Human beings are one of the most intelligent and creative species on Earth, and their history and evolution have always been topics of interest for scientists. Where did humans come from? Where are humans going? These questions may never have definite answers, but we can speculate about the future of humanity by studying their past and present. ​ According to scientific evidence, humans first appeared in Africa about 300,000 years ago, when they belonged to the species Homo sapiens. Homo sapiens are the only surviving species of the genus Homo, but not the first one. Before Homo sapiens, there were several other species of Homo, such as Homo erectus, Homo heidelbergensis and Homo neanderthalensis. These species are all extinct now, but they may have had genetic exchanges with Homo sapiens. ​ In the past few million years, humans have undergone many significant changes and adaptations to cope with different environments and challenges. For example, humans developed features such as upright walking, dexterous fingers and complex language. These features enabled humans to make tools, hunt food, build societies and cultures, and explore the mysteries of nature. ​ So, what kind of changes will humans experience in the next few million years? This question is hard to answer, because the future is unpredictable and depends on many factors, such as natural selection, genetic mutation, environmental change, technological development, etc. However, some futurists have proposed some possibilities and scenarios that allow us to imagine what the future of humanity might look like. ​ One possibility is that humans will become smaller, thinner, paler and longer-lived. This might be because in a highly developed and crowded world, a small body can save energy and space, while a pale skin can absorb more vitamin D. Moreover, medical and genetic technology might also extend human lifespan and health. ​ Another possibility is that humans will become hybrid beings of half-mechanical and half-biological parts. This might be because in a highly competitive and complex world, humans need to rely on high-tech implants or replacements to enhance their abilities and adaptability. For example, humans might have mechanical eyes that can take photos, zoom in or see different frequencies of light; or mechanical limbs that can regenerate, transform or increase strength. ​ Of course, these are just some speculations, not certain predictions. The future of humanity might have many different directions and possibilities, and it might also be affected by some unforeseeable events or disasters. Therefore, humans need to maintain an open and flexible attitude to deal with the uncertainty and change of the future. ​ The past and future of humanity is a fascinating topic that can help us understand our origin and destiny, as well as stimulate our imagination and creativity. By reading this article, you might have learned more about the history and evolution of humanity, and you might also have more curiosity and expectation about the future of humanity. In any case, we should cherish our identity and traits as human beings, while also respecting and protecting the Earth and other living beings that we share it with.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Artificial Intelligence Opportunities and Challenges</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/AI-Opportunities-and-Challenges/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Artificial Intelligence Opportunities and Challenges" /><published>2023-07-13T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-13T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/AI-Opportunities-and-Challenges</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/AI-Opportunities-and-Challenges/">&lt;p&gt;​	Artificial intelligence (AI) is the intelligent behavior performed by computer systems or machines, such as learning, reasoning, perception, creativity, etc. The development of AI can be traced back to the 1940s, when Turing proposed a famous question: Can machines think? Since then, AI has become a major field of computer science, with various applications and implications in different domains. In this passage, we will explore some of the opportunities and challenges that AI brings to our society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	One of the main opportunities that AI offers is to enhance human capabilities and productivity. AI can perform tasks that are difficult, dangerous, or tedious for humans, such as medical diagnosis, industrial automation, online customer service, etc. AI can also augment human intelligence and creativity, by providing insights, suggestions, or solutions that humans may not think of. For example, AI can help scientists discover new drugs, artists create new genres of music, or educators design personalized learning plans. By leveraging AI, humans can achieve more with less time and effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	Another opportunity that AI provides is to improve social welfare and quality of life. AI can help address some of the global challenges that we face today, such as poverty, hunger, climate change, health care, education, etc. AI can also enhance our personal well-being and happiness, by offering entertainment, convenience, or companionship. For example, AI can help farmers increase crop yields, doctors treat diseases, teachers educate students, or gamers enjoy immersive experiences. By using AI, we can make our world a better place to live in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	However, AI also poses some significant challenges that we need to be aware of and deal with. One of the main challenges is the ethical and moral issues that arise from the use and misuse of AI. AI can have positive or negative impacts on human values and rights, depending on how it is designed and deployed. For example, AI can help prevent crimes, protect privacy, or promote fairness; but it can also enable surveillance, discrimination, or manipulation. Therefore, we need to ensure that AI is aligned with our ethical principles and social norms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	Another challenge that AI presents is the social and economic implications that result from the displacement and transformation of human labor. AI can replace or complement human workers in various sectors and occupations,depending on the level of skill and creativity required. For example, AI can automate routine and repetitive tasks, such as data entry, accounting, or driving; but it can also enhance complex and creative tasks, such as engineering, design, or writing. Therefore, we need to prepare for the changes and opportunities that AI will bring to our work and education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;​	In conclusion, AI is a powerful and influential technology that can bring both opportunities and challenges to our society. We need to embrace the benefits and mitigate the risks of AI, by developing and using it responsibly and wisely. We also need to adapt and learn from AI, by acquiring new skills and knowledge that will enable us to thrive in the era of artificial intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html">​ Artificial intelligence (AI) is the intelligent behavior performed by computer systems or machines, such as learning, reasoning, perception, creativity, etc. The development of AI can be traced back to the 1940s, when Turing proposed a famous question: Can machines think? Since then, AI has become a major field of computer science, with various applications and implications in different domains. In this passage, we will explore some of the opportunities and challenges that AI brings to our society. ​ One of the main opportunities that AI offers is to enhance human capabilities and productivity. AI can perform tasks that are difficult, dangerous, or tedious for humans, such as medical diagnosis, industrial automation, online customer service, etc. AI can also augment human intelligence and creativity, by providing insights, suggestions, or solutions that humans may not think of. For example, AI can help scientists discover new drugs, artists create new genres of music, or educators design personalized learning plans. By leveraging AI, humans can achieve more with less time and effort. ​ Another opportunity that AI provides is to improve social welfare and quality of life. AI can help address some of the global challenges that we face today, such as poverty, hunger, climate change, health care, education, etc. AI can also enhance our personal well-being and happiness, by offering entertainment, convenience, or companionship. For example, AI can help farmers increase crop yields, doctors treat diseases, teachers educate students, or gamers enjoy immersive experiences. By using AI, we can make our world a better place to live in. ​ However, AI also poses some significant challenges that we need to be aware of and deal with. One of the main challenges is the ethical and moral issues that arise from the use and misuse of AI. AI can have positive or negative impacts on human values and rights, depending on how it is designed and deployed. For example, AI can help prevent crimes, protect privacy, or promote fairness; but it can also enable surveillance, discrimination, or manipulation. Therefore, we need to ensure that AI is aligned with our ethical principles and social norms. ​ Another challenge that AI presents is the social and economic implications that result from the displacement and transformation of human labor. AI can replace or complement human workers in various sectors and occupations,depending on the level of skill and creativity required. For example, AI can automate routine and repetitive tasks, such as data entry, accounting, or driving; but it can also enhance complex and creative tasks, such as engineering, design, or writing. Therefore, we need to prepare for the changes and opportunities that AI will bring to our work and education. ​ In conclusion, AI is a powerful and influential technology that can bring both opportunities and challenges to our society. We need to embrace the benefits and mitigate the risks of AI, by developing and using it responsibly and wisely. We also need to adapt and learn from AI, by acquiring new skills and knowledge that will enable us to thrive in the era of artificial intelligence.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">关于个人博客的构思</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/guanyugerenbokedegousi/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="关于个人博客的构思" /><published>2022-06-08T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2022-06-08T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/guanyugerenbokedegousi</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/guanyugerenbokedegousi/">&lt;!-- &lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt; --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;构建博客的初心是为了记录有关于生活和技术的。&lt;br /&gt;
在选择构建博客的时候，由于&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;github pages&lt;/code&gt; 对 &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll&lt;/code&gt;的官方支持，于是选择用jekyll构建出它。
本着极简主义的理念，博客应该以“内容”为主，而不是花里胡哨的页面和动效。 所幸 jekyll themes 里有着一个还算简洁的主题 &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;contrast&lt;/code&gt;,
但还不够简洁，于是在此主题里做了一点修改:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;不再展示sidebar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;不再展示内容摘要&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;将网页上方常驻内容的bar的颜色修改为浅色&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;将网页上方常驻内容的bar的高度进行了修改&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;将网页上方常驻内容的bar里的字体进行了修改，使得更协调&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;不再展示 展示&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Mail&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/code&gt;的bar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;修改了&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;page&lt;/code&gt;页面，使其不再重复展示&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;page.title&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;修改了&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;post&lt;/code&gt;页面，使得其展示的标题更着眼&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;修改了&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;post&lt;/code&gt;页面，标题不再具有链接属性&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;修改了&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;post&lt;/code&gt;页面，使其不再重复展示&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;page.time&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;修改了标题H1…H2等等字体粗度&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;修改了正文文字的字体粗度&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;将&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;单个页面title | 网站titlle&lt;/code&gt;的样式改为了&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;单个页面title&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;于是一个极为简洁的博客就此诞生了！！！
但是，偶然的突发奇想，使得我想记录自己的任务进度完成情况，
这并不是简单的&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;todo list&lt;/code&gt;(如果是这样的话,markdown即可)，所以它是甘特图！！！其实有两种方法解决它：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;使用其他甘特图之类的软件，每次更新博客的时候把任务进度的附图贴上&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;构建数据库，再重新撰写相关代码(很复杂的感觉，而且就不以静态网站来呈现了)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;于是解决方法&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;1&lt;/code&gt;的不完美和&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;2&lt;/code&gt;的复杂，所以此想法先搁置！！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;目前还有更多的学习任务！等完成此以后再来！！&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html">构建博客的初心是为了记录有关于生活和技术的。 在选择构建博客的时候，由于github pages 对 jekyll的官方支持，于是选择用jekyll构建出它。 本着极简主义的理念，博客应该以“内容”为主，而不是花里胡哨的页面和动效。 所幸 jekyll themes 里有着一个还算简洁的主题 contrast, 但还不够简洁，于是在此主题里做了一点修改: 不再展示sidebar 不再展示内容摘要 将网页上方常驻内容的bar的颜色修改为浅色 将网页上方常驻内容的bar的高度进行了修改 将网页上方常驻内容的bar里的字体进行了修改，使得更协调 不再展示 展示Mail、Github的bar 修改了page页面，使其不再重复展示page.title 修改了post页面，使得其展示的标题更着眼 修改了post页面，标题不再具有链接属性 修改了post页面，使其不再重复展示page.time 修改了标题H1…H2等等字体粗度 修改了正文文字的字体粗度 将单个页面title | 网站titlle的样式改为了单个页面title 于是一个极为简洁的博客就此诞生了！！！ 但是，偶然的突发奇想，使得我想记录自己的任务进度完成情况， 这并不是简单的todo list(如果是这样的话,markdown即可)，所以它是甘特图！！！其实有两种方法解决它： 使用其他甘特图之类的软件，每次更新博客的时候把任务进度的附图贴上 构建数据库，再重新撰写相关代码(很复杂的感觉，而且就不以静态网站来呈现了) 于是解决方法1的不完美和2的复杂，所以此想法先搁置！！ 目前还有更多的学习任务！等完成此以后再来！！</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">画江湖之不良人之岐王李茂贞</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Qiwang-limaozhen-Huajianghu/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="画江湖之不良人之岐王李茂贞" /><published>2022-06-05T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2022-06-05T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Qiwang-limaozhen-Huajianghu</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Qiwang-limaozhen-Huajianghu/">&lt;p&gt;动漫『画江湖之不良人』第三季中，出现了———真·岐王·李茂贞，为什么说是“真”岐王呢，因为之前所出现的岐王其实都是他的妹妹假扮的。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;岐王这个角色其实塑造的非常有魅力，在唐末战乱不止的时候，岐王屡立奇功，后又在岐国鼎盛时期离开岐国前往「娆疆」寻找可以打开「龙泉宝盒」的方法。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;归来&quot;&gt;归来&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;岐王出走岐国16年，背井离乡饱受折磨，终寻得解蛊之道，于是归来。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;归途第一站便是寻得「龙泉宝盒」，而岐王得知的消息是：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;乾陵一战后「龙泉宝盒」出世&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;宝盒在 假·李星云、孟婆、李思源 等人的手里
于是岐王找到了他们，并置换拿回宝盒的条件。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;分析&quot;&gt;分析&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;在最后一场大战中，岐王面对妹妹————女帝说出:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;你明知我不愿意与你为敌&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;好久没写作了。。。文笔不好，不知道从哪写起又怎样以优雅的文笔通顺的逻辑来写。。。
待续。。。&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html">动漫『画江湖之不良人』第三季中，出现了———真·岐王·李茂贞，为什么说是“真”岐王呢，因为之前所出现的岐王其实都是他的妹妹假扮的。 岐王这个角色其实塑造的非常有魅力，在唐末战乱不止的时候，岐王屡立奇功，后又在岐国鼎盛时期离开岐国前往「娆疆」寻找可以打开「龙泉宝盒」的方法。</summary></entry></feed>