<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="zh"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="zh" /><updated>2023-09-04T16:12:01+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">当渐行渐远的风不再歌唱</title><subtitle>确实，我还在成长</subtitle><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><entry><title type="html">What kind of people are likely to achieve nothing in life?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/What-kind-of-people-are-likely-to-achieve-nothing-in-life/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What kind of people are likely to achieve nothing in life?" /><published>2023-07-29T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-29T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/What%20kind%20of%20people%20are%20likely%20to%20achieve%20nothing%20in%20life</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/What-kind-of-people-are-likely-to-achieve-nothing-in-life/">&lt;p&gt; Many people have dreams and aspirations for their lives, but not everyone can achieve them. Some people may face various obstacles and challenges that prevent them from reaching their goals, while others may lack the motivation or the ability to pursue them. However, there is also a group of people who may seem to have the potential and the opportunity to succeed, but end up achieving nothing in life. Who are these people and why do they fail?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; One possible answer is that these people are deep thinkers who have a high level of understanding and awareness, but a low level of experience and action. They may have a lot of knowledge and insights about various aspects of life, but they do not apply them to their own situations or problems. They may think too much and too fast, but do not act enough or at all. They may be detached from reality and feel helpless and powerless. They may be afraid of failure and disappointment, and doubt themselves and their abilities. They may be trapped in their own minds and lose sight of their goals and passions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; This answer is based on a paragraph that you provided, which claims that a deep-thinking young person is more likely to fail in life because their soul is ahead of their age. The paragraph suggests that the more one knows, the more one fears; the more one thinks, the less one acts; the more one understands, the less one achieves. The paragraph also suggests that the solution is to lower one’s head, practice more, contact more, feel more, and focus on the present and the mundane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, this answer is not convincing or accurate for several reasons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; First, being a deep thinker does not necessarily mean being a failure. In fact, many successful people in history were also deep thinkers who had profound insights into various aspects of life. For example, Albert Einstein was not only a brilliant physicist who revolutionized science, but also a philosopher who pondered on the meaning of existence. Martin Luther King Jr. was not only a charismatic leader who fought for civil rights, but also a theologian who reflected on the nature of justice. Oprah Winfrey was not only a media mogul who built an empire, but also a spiritual seeker who explored the essence of happiness. These examples show that being a deep thinker can actually enhance one’s success, rather than hinder it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Second, knowing more does not necessarily mean fearing more. In fact, many studies have shown that knowledge can reduce fear and increase confidence. For example, a study by researchers at Stanford University found that learning about the brain mechanisms of fear can help people overcome their phobias. Another study by researchers at Yale University found that learning about the causes and consequences of climate change can motivate people to take action to mitigate it. These examples show that knowledge can actually empower people to face their fears, rather than increase them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Third, thinking more does not necessarily mean acting less. In fact, both are essential components of any meaningful endeavor. Thinking can help us plan, analyze, evaluate, and improve our actions. Acting can help us test, apply, verify, and refine our thoughts. For example, Thomas Edison was not only a prolific inventor who created many useful devices, but also an avid experimenter who conducted thousands of trials. Mahatma Gandhi was not only a visionary thinker who advocated for nonviolence and independence, but also an active practitioner who led many campaigns. These examples show that thinking and acting can actually complement each other, rather than oppose each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Fourth, lowering one’s head, practicing more, contacting more, feeling more, and focusing on the present and the mundane are not necessarily the best ways to achieve success. In fact, these actions may limit one’s potential and creativity, and make one conform to the norms and expectations of the society, rather than challenge or question them. They may also make one lose sight of the future and the sublime, and miss out on the opportunities and possibilities that lie ahead. Therefore, one should not choose between following or leading, between conforming or challenging, between focusing on the present or the future, or between the mundane or the sublime. One should do both, depending on the context and the purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; The question of what kind of people are likely to achieve nothing in life is a complex and subjective one that has no definitive answer. It depends on one’s perspective and criteria, as well as on the factors that influence one’s success or failure, such as motivation, talent, opportunity, luck, etc. However, one possible answer that is not convincing or accurate is that deep thinkers who know more, think more, and understand more are more likely to fail in life. This answer is based on a simplistic and pessimistic view of knowledge, thinking, and understanding, and a narrow and rigid view of success, action, and reality. A more balanced and nuanced view would recognize that being a deep thinker can be an advantage, rather than a disadvantage, as long as it is coupled with action and practice; that knowing more can be a blessing, rather than a curse, as long as it is used wisely and responsibly; and that one should not limit oneself to one way of being or doing, but embrace the diversity and complexity of life.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html"> Many people have dreams and aspirations for their lives, but not everyone can achieve them. Some people may face various obstacles and challenges that prevent them from reaching their goals, while others may lack the motivation or the ability to pursue them. However, there is also a group of people who may seem to have the potential and the opportunity to succeed, but end up achieving nothing in life. Who are these people and why do they fail?  One possible answer is that these people are deep thinkers who have a high level of understanding and awareness, but a low level of experience and action. They may have a lot of knowledge and insights about various aspects of life, but they do not apply them to their own situations or problems. They may think too much and too fast, but do not act enough or at all. They may be detached from reality and feel helpless and powerless. They may be afraid of failure and disappointment, and doubt themselves and their abilities. They may be trapped in their own minds and lose sight of their goals and passions.  This answer is based on a paragraph that you provided, which claims that a deep-thinking young person is more likely to fail in life because their soul is ahead of their age. The paragraph suggests that the more one knows, the more one fears; the more one thinks, the less one acts; the more one understands, the less one achieves. The paragraph also suggests that the solution is to lower one’s head, practice more, contact more, feel more, and focus on the present and the mundane. However, this answer is not convincing or accurate for several reasons:  First, being a deep thinker does not necessarily mean being a failure. In fact, many successful people in history were also deep thinkers who had profound insights into various aspects of life. For example, Albert Einstein was not only a brilliant physicist who revolutionized science, but also a philosopher who pondered on the meaning of existence. Martin Luther King Jr. was not only a charismatic leader who fought for civil rights, but also a theologian who reflected on the nature of justice. Oprah Winfrey was not only a media mogul who built an empire, but also a spiritual seeker who explored the essence of happiness. These examples show that being a deep thinker can actually enhance one’s success, rather than hinder it.  Second, knowing more does not necessarily mean fearing more. In fact, many studies have shown that knowledge can reduce fear and increase confidence. For example, a study by researchers at Stanford University found that learning about the brain mechanisms of fear can help people overcome their phobias. Another study by researchers at Yale University found that learning about the causes and consequences of climate change can motivate people to take action to mitigate it. These examples show that knowledge can actually empower people to face their fears, rather than increase them.  Third, thinking more does not necessarily mean acting less. In fact, both are essential components of any meaningful endeavor. Thinking can help us plan, analyze, evaluate, and improve our actions. Acting can help us test, apply, verify, and refine our thoughts. For example, Thomas Edison was not only a prolific inventor who created many useful devices, but also an avid experimenter who conducted thousands of trials. Mahatma Gandhi was not only a visionary thinker who advocated for nonviolence and independence, but also an active practitioner who led many campaigns. These examples show that thinking and acting can actually complement each other, rather than oppose each other.  Fourth, lowering one’s head, practicing more, contacting more, feeling more, and focusing on the present and the mundane are not necessarily the best ways to achieve success. In fact, these actions may limit one’s potential and creativity, and make one conform to the norms and expectations of the society, rather than challenge or question them. They may also make one lose sight of the future and the sublime, and miss out on the opportunities and possibilities that lie ahead. Therefore, one should not choose between following or leading, between conforming or challenging, between focusing on the present or the future, or between the mundane or the sublime. One should do both, depending on the context and the purpose. Conclusion  The question of what kind of people are likely to achieve nothing in life is a complex and subjective one that has no definitive answer. It depends on one’s perspective and criteria, as well as on the factors that influence one’s success or failure, such as motivation, talent, opportunity, luck, etc. However, one possible answer that is not convincing or accurate is that deep thinkers who know more, think more, and understand more are more likely to fail in life. This answer is based on a simplistic and pessimistic view of knowledge, thinking, and understanding, and a narrow and rigid view of success, action, and reality. A more balanced and nuanced view would recognize that being a deep thinker can be an advantage, rather than a disadvantage, as long as it is coupled with action and practice; that knowing more can be a blessing, rather than a curse, as long as it is used wisely and responsibly; and that one should not limit oneself to one way of being or doing, but embrace the diversity and complexity of life.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Can Merit Make Up for Mistakes?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Can-Merit-Make-Up-for-Mistakes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Can Merit Make Up for Mistakes?" /><published>2023-07-28T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-28T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Can%20Merit%20Make%20Up%20for%20Mistakes</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Can-Merit-Make-Up-for-Mistakes/">&lt;p&gt; There is a Chinese idiom that says “以功补过” (yǐ gōng bǔ guò), which means to use merit to make up for mistakes. It implies that one can redeem oneself from one’s faults or errors by doing good deeds or achieving great results. But is this really possible? Can merit truly make up for mistakes? Or are mistakes irreversible and irreparable? In this essay, we will explore these questions from different perspectives and examine the philosophical implications of this idiom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; First, we need to define what merit and mistake mean. Merit can be defined as the quality or state of being worthy, valuable, or commendable. It can also refer to the act or achievement that demonstrates such quality or state. Mistake can be defined as the act or judgment that is wrong, erroneous, or faulty. It can also refer to the consequence or outcome of such act or judgment. Merit and mistake are often relative and subjective concepts, as they depend on the standards, criteria, and expectations of different people, groups, or situations. For example, what is considered as merit in one culture may be considered as mistake in another culture. What is considered as merit in one context may be considered as mistake in another context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Second, we need to consider the conditions and factors that affect whether merit can make up for mistake. One possible condition is the proportionality between merit and mistake. This means that the merit should be equal or greater than the mistake in terms of magnitude, impact, or significance. For example, if one makes a small mistake, such as forgetting to do a homework assignment, one may be able to make up for it by doing an extra credit project or helping a classmate with their homework. However, if one makes a big mistake, such as cheating on an exam or plagiarizing a paper, one may not be able to make up for it by doing any amount of good deeds or achievements. Another possible condition is the relevance between merit and mistake. This means that the merit should be related or connected to the mistake in terms of cause, effect, or domain. For example, if one makes a mistake in one’s work, such as missing a deadline or making a wrong calculation, one may be able to make up for it by improving one’s performance or correcting one’s error in the same work. However, if one makes a mistake in one’s personal life, such as hurting someone’s feelings or breaking someone’s trust, one may not be able to make up for it by doing anything in one’s work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Third, we need to reflect on the philosophical implications of this idiom. One possible implication is the moral dimension of merit and mistake. This means that merit and mistake are not only objective or factual phenomena, but also subjective or ethical judgments. Merit and mistake involve not only what one does or achieves, but also why one does or achieves it. Merit and mistake imply not only the consequences or outcomes of one’s actions or decisions, but also the intentions or motivations behind them. Therefore, merit and mistake are not only measured by external standards or criteria, but also by internal values or principles. For example, if one does something good or great for selfish or ulterior reasons, such as fame, money, or power, one may not be truly meritorious. If one does something wrong or bad for noble or altruistic reasons, such as justice, compassion, or sacrifice, one may not be truly mistaken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Another possible implication is the existential dimension of merit and mistake. This means that merit and mistake are not only isolated or discrete events, but also continuous or dynamic processes. Merit and mistake involve not only what one has done or achieved in the past, but also what one is doing or achieving in the present and what one will do or achieve in the future. Merit and mistake imply not only the state or condition of one’s being, but also the direction or potential of one’s becoming. Therefore, merit and mistake are not only evaluated by static or fixed standards, but also by dynamic or evolving standards. For example, if one does something good or great in the past, but fails to maintain or improve it in the present or future, one may lose one’s merit. If one does something wrong or bad in the past, but learns from it and changes for the better in the present or future, one may overcome one’s mistake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; In conclusion, merit and mistake are complex and multifaceted concepts that depend on various factors and conditions. Whether merit can make up for mistake is not a simple or universal question, but a nuanced and contextual question. However, some general principles that can help us answer it are to be aware of the proportionality and relevance between merit and mistake, to be mindful of the moral and existential dimensions of merit and mistake, and to be humble and honest about our merits and mistakes. Merit and mistake are not mutually exclusive or incompatible, but mutually influential and interdependent.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html"> There is a Chinese idiom that says “以功补过” (yǐ gōng bǔ guò), which means to use merit to make up for mistakes. It implies that one can redeem oneself from one’s faults or errors by doing good deeds or achieving great results. But is this really possible? Can merit truly make up for mistakes? Or are mistakes irreversible and irreparable? In this essay, we will explore these questions from different perspectives and examine the philosophical implications of this idiom.  First, we need to define what merit and mistake mean. Merit can be defined as the quality or state of being worthy, valuable, or commendable. It can also refer to the act or achievement that demonstrates such quality or state. Mistake can be defined as the act or judgment that is wrong, erroneous, or faulty. It can also refer to the consequence or outcome of such act or judgment. Merit and mistake are often relative and subjective concepts, as they depend on the standards, criteria, and expectations of different people, groups, or situations. For example, what is considered as merit in one culture may be considered as mistake in another culture. What is considered as merit in one context may be considered as mistake in another context.  Second, we need to consider the conditions and factors that affect whether merit can make up for mistake. One possible condition is the proportionality between merit and mistake. This means that the merit should be equal or greater than the mistake in terms of magnitude, impact, or significance. For example, if one makes a small mistake, such as forgetting to do a homework assignment, one may be able to make up for it by doing an extra credit project or helping a classmate with their homework. However, if one makes a big mistake, such as cheating on an exam or plagiarizing a paper, one may not be able to make up for it by doing any amount of good deeds or achievements. Another possible condition is the relevance between merit and mistake. This means that the merit should be related or connected to the mistake in terms of cause, effect, or domain. For example, if one makes a mistake in one’s work, such as missing a deadline or making a wrong calculation, one may be able to make up for it by improving one’s performance or correcting one’s error in the same work. However, if one makes a mistake in one’s personal life, such as hurting someone’s feelings or breaking someone’s trust, one may not be able to make up for it by doing anything in one’s work.  Third, we need to reflect on the philosophical implications of this idiom. One possible implication is the moral dimension of merit and mistake. This means that merit and mistake are not only objective or factual phenomena, but also subjective or ethical judgments. Merit and mistake involve not only what one does or achieves, but also why one does or achieves it. Merit and mistake imply not only the consequences or outcomes of one’s actions or decisions, but also the intentions or motivations behind them. Therefore, merit and mistake are not only measured by external standards or criteria, but also by internal values or principles. For example, if one does something good or great for selfish or ulterior reasons, such as fame, money, or power, one may not be truly meritorious. If one does something wrong or bad for noble or altruistic reasons, such as justice, compassion, or sacrifice, one may not be truly mistaken.  Another possible implication is the existential dimension of merit and mistake. This means that merit and mistake are not only isolated or discrete events, but also continuous or dynamic processes. Merit and mistake involve not only what one has done or achieved in the past, but also what one is doing or achieving in the present and what one will do or achieve in the future. Merit and mistake imply not only the state or condition of one’s being, but also the direction or potential of one’s becoming. Therefore, merit and mistake are not only evaluated by static or fixed standards, but also by dynamic or evolving standards. For example, if one does something good or great in the past, but fails to maintain or improve it in the present or future, one may lose one’s merit. If one does something wrong or bad in the past, but learns from it and changes for the better in the present or future, one may overcome one’s mistake.  In conclusion, merit and mistake are complex and multifaceted concepts that depend on various factors and conditions. Whether merit can make up for mistake is not a simple or universal question, but a nuanced and contextual question. However, some general principles that can help us answer it are to be aware of the proportionality and relevance between merit and mistake, to be mindful of the moral and existential dimensions of merit and mistake, and to be humble and honest about our merits and mistakes. Merit and mistake are not mutually exclusive or incompatible, but mutually influential and interdependent.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Violence Begets Violence: Is It Justice?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Violence-Begets-Violence-Is-It-Justice/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Violence Begets Violence: Is It Justice?" /><published>2023-07-27T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-27T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Violence%20Begets%20Violence%20Is%20It%20Justice</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Violence-Begets-Violence-Is-It-Justice/">&lt;p&gt; Violence is a phenomenon that has plagued human history and society, causing pain, suffering, and death to countless individuals and groups. Violence can be defined as the use of physical force or power to harm or coerce others, or the threat of such use. Violence can take many forms, such as war, terrorism, crime, abuse, torture, and self-harm. Violence can have various motives, such as revenge, hatred, greed, fear, or ideology. Violence can have various consequences, such as injury, trauma, disability, or death. Violence can also have various impacts, such as psychological, social, economic, or political. Violence is a complex and multifaceted issue that raises many ethical and moral questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; One of the most controversial questions is whether violence can be justified or legitimate in certain situations or contexts. Is it ever right to use violence against those who use violence? Is it ever fair to repay violence with violence? Is it ever moral to fight fire with fire? In other words, is violence begets violence a form of justice?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Some people may argue that violence begets violence is indeed a form of justice. They may claim that violence is the only way to deal with violence, as it can deter, punish, or eliminate the perpetrators of violence. They may assert that violence is the only language that the violent understand, as they do not respect reason or morality. They may cite the famous saying: “跟讲德之人讲理，跟无德之人讲武” (Talk reason with those who are virtuous, talk force with those who are vicious). They may give examples of historical or contemporary cases where violence was used to achieve justice, such as the American Revolution, the French Revolution, the anti-colonial struggles, the anti-apartheid movement, the civil rights movement, the feminist movement, the environmental movement, or the human rights movement. They may contend that violence begets violence is a form of self-defense, resistance, or liberation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; However, other people may argue that violence begets violence is not a form of justice. They may claim that violence is never the solution to violence, as it can only escalate, perpetuate, or exacerbate the cycle of violence. They may assert that violence is never the answer to violence, as it can only breed more hatred, resentment, or revenge. They may cite the famous saying: “An eye for an eye makes the whole world blind” (attributed to Mahatma Gandhi). They may give examples of historical or contemporary cases where violence failed to achieve justice, such as the World Wars, the Cold War, the Vietnam War, the Iraq War, the Syrian Civil War, the Israeli-Palestinian conflict, the Rwandan genocide, the Darfur crisis, or the War on Terror. They may contend that violence begets violence is a form of aggression, oppression, or domination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; What does the evidence say about these arguments? There is no definitive answer to this question, as different situations and contexts may have different outcomes and implications. However, some recent studies and books have suggested that nonviolence is more effective and sustainable than violence in achieving justice and social change . For example, researchers have found that nonviolent campaigns are more likely to succeed than violent ones in achieving political and social change , that nonviolent campaigns are more inclusive and participatory than violent ones, that nonviolent campaigns are more likely to foster democratic institutions and human rights than violent ones, and that nonviolent campaigns are more likely to reduce the risk of civil war and repression than violent ones. These findings imply that nonviolence begets nonviolence, and that nonviolence is a form of justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; In conclusion, violence begets violence is a contentious and complex issue that has no simple or universal answer. However, some general principles that can help us evaluate it are to be aware of the nature, motives, consequences, and impacts of violence, to seek or create alternatives to violence, to respect the dignity and rights of all human beings, and to promote peace and harmony. Violence begets violence is not a form of justice, but a form of injustice.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html"> Violence is a phenomenon that has plagued human history and society, causing pain, suffering, and death to countless individuals and groups. Violence can be defined as the use of physical force or power to harm or coerce others, or the threat of such use. Violence can take many forms, such as war, terrorism, crime, abuse, torture, and self-harm. Violence can have various motives, such as revenge, hatred, greed, fear, or ideology. Violence can have various consequences, such as injury, trauma, disability, or death. Violence can also have various impacts, such as psychological, social, economic, or political. Violence is a complex and multifaceted issue that raises many ethical and moral questions.  One of the most controversial questions is whether violence can be justified or legitimate in certain situations or contexts. Is it ever right to use violence against those who use violence? Is it ever fair to repay violence with violence? Is it ever moral to fight fire with fire? In other words, is violence begets violence a form of justice?  Some people may argue that violence begets violence is indeed a form of justice. They may claim that violence is the only way to deal with violence, as it can deter, punish, or eliminate the perpetrators of violence. They may assert that violence is the only language that the violent understand, as they do not respect reason or morality. They may cite the famous saying: “跟讲德之人讲理，跟无德之人讲武” (Talk reason with those who are virtuous, talk force with those who are vicious). They may give examples of historical or contemporary cases where violence was used to achieve justice, such as the American Revolution, the French Revolution, the anti-colonial struggles, the anti-apartheid movement, the civil rights movement, the feminist movement, the environmental movement, or the human rights movement. They may contend that violence begets violence is a form of self-defense, resistance, or liberation.  However, other people may argue that violence begets violence is not a form of justice. They may claim that violence is never the solution to violence, as it can only escalate, perpetuate, or exacerbate the cycle of violence. They may assert that violence is never the answer to violence, as it can only breed more hatred, resentment, or revenge. They may cite the famous saying: “An eye for an eye makes the whole world blind” (attributed to Mahatma Gandhi). They may give examples of historical or contemporary cases where violence failed to achieve justice, such as the World Wars, the Cold War, the Vietnam War, the Iraq War, the Syrian Civil War, the Israeli-Palestinian conflict, the Rwandan genocide, the Darfur crisis, or the War on Terror. They may contend that violence begets violence is a form of aggression, oppression, or domination.  What does the evidence say about these arguments? There is no definitive answer to this question, as different situations and contexts may have different outcomes and implications. However, some recent studies and books have suggested that nonviolence is more effective and sustainable than violence in achieving justice and social change . For example, researchers have found that nonviolent campaigns are more likely to succeed than violent ones in achieving political and social change , that nonviolent campaigns are more inclusive and participatory than violent ones, that nonviolent campaigns are more likely to foster democratic institutions and human rights than violent ones, and that nonviolent campaigns are more likely to reduce the risk of civil war and repression than violent ones. These findings imply that nonviolence begets nonviolence, and that nonviolence is a form of justice.  In conclusion, violence begets violence is a contentious and complex issue that has no simple or universal answer. However, some general principles that can help us evaluate it are to be aware of the nature, motives, consequences, and impacts of violence, to seek or create alternatives to violence, to respect the dignity and rights of all human beings, and to promote peace and harmony. Violence begets violence is not a form of justice, but a form of injustice.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fate or Free Will: What Determines Success?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Fate-or-Free-Will-What-Determines-Success/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fate or Free Will: What Determines Success?" /><published>2023-07-26T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-26T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Fate%20or%20Free%20Will%20What%20Determines%20Success</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Fate-or-Free-Will-What-Determines-Success/">&lt;p&gt; Success is a highly sought-after goal in life, but what does it take to achieve it? Is it a matter of fate or free will? Do we have control over our destiny, or are we subject to the whims of chance and luck? These are some of the questions that have fascinated philosophers, scientists, and ordinary people for centuries. In this essay, we will explore different perspectives on the role of fate and free will in success, and examine the evidence from various fields and domains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; One perspective is that success is largely determined by fate, or the predetermined course of events that is beyond human control. This view is often associated with the concept of “tian dao” (天道), or the way of heaven, in Chinese philosophy. According to this view, there is a cosmic order that governs everything in the universe, and humans must align themselves with it to achieve harmony and prosperity. Those who violate this order will face misfortune and failure. Therefore, success is not a matter of personal choice or effort, but a matter of following the natural laws and principles that are set by a higher power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Another perspective is that success is largely determined by free will, or the ability to act according to one’s own desires and preferences. This view is often associated with the concept of “ba dao” (霸道), or the way of hegemony, in Chinese philosophy. According to this view, there is no fixed destiny or fate for anyone, and humans can shape their own future by exercising their will and power. Those who are ambitious and courageous can overcome any obstacles and challenges that they encounter, and achieve success by their own merits. Therefore, success is not a matter of external factors or luck, but a matter of personal agency and responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; A third perspective is that success is a result of both fate and free will, or a combination of predetermined and contingent factors. This view acknowledges that there are some aspects of life that are beyond human control, such as genetics, environment, culture, and historical circumstances. However, it also recognizes that there are some aspects of life that are within human control, such as education, skills, habits, attitudes, and decisions. Those who are successful are able to make use of both their given advantages and their acquired abilities, and adapt to changing situations and opportunities. Therefore, success is not a matter of either-or, but a matter of both-and.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; What does the evidence say about these perspectives? There is no definitive answer to this question, as different fields and domains may have different criteria and measures of success. However, some recent studies and books have suggested that luck plays a far greater role in success than most people realize. For example, researchers have found that about half of the differences in income across people worldwide is explained by their country of residence and by the income distribution within that country, that scientific impact is randomly distributed, that the chance of becoming a CEO is influenced by your name or month of birth, and that huge success in business is largely based on luck. These findings imply that success is not only a function of talent or skill, but also a function of opportunity or circumstance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Does this mean that luck is everything? Not necessarily. Luck can be seen as a part of ability, rather than an opposite or alternative to it. Ability can be defined as the capacity to perform well in a given situation or domain. However, this capacity depends not only on one’s innate or acquired traits, but also on one’s environment or context. For example, being born with perfect pitch may be an advantage for a musician, but not for a mathematician. Similarly, being born in a wealthy country may be an advantage for an entrepreneur, but not for an artist. Therefore, ability can be seen as a function of both fit and luck. Fit refers to how well one’s traits match the demands or expectations of one’s situation or domain. Luck refers to how favorable one’s situation or domain is for one’s traits. Those who are successful are able to find or create situations or domains that fit their traits well and offer them favorable opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; What about choice? Is it more important than effort? And is choice predetermined or free? These are difficult questions to answer, as they involve metaphysical and ethical issues that are beyond the scope of this essay. However, one possible way to approach them is to adopt a pragmatic perspective. According to this perspective, choice is not an abstract concept that exists independently of reality, but a concrete action that occurs in specific contexts. Choice is not something that we have or don’t have in general, but something that we do or don’t do in particular situations. Choice is not something that we can prove or disprove objectively, but something that we can evaluate or justify subjectively. Therefore, choice is not a matter of fate or free will, but a matter of pragmatism or rationality. Pragmatism refers to how well one’s choices work or succeed in one’s reality. Rationality refers to how well one’s choices are consistent or coherent with one’s values and goals. Those who are successful are able to make choices that are both pragmatic and rational, and that balance the trade-offs between effort and opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; In conclusion, success is a complex and multifaceted phenomenon that depends on various factors, such as fate, free will, luck, ability, fit, choice, effort, and opportunity. There is no simple or universal formula for success, as different situations and domains may require different strategies and skills. However, some general principles that can help us achieve success are to be aware of our strengths and weaknesses, to seek or create favorable environments and contexts, to make pragmatic and rational choices, and to adapt and learn from our experiences. Success is not a fixed or predetermined outcome, but a dynamic and evolving process.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html"> Success is a highly sought-after goal in life, but what does it take to achieve it? Is it a matter of fate or free will? Do we have control over our destiny, or are we subject to the whims of chance and luck? These are some of the questions that have fascinated philosophers, scientists, and ordinary people for centuries. In this essay, we will explore different perspectives on the role of fate and free will in success, and examine the evidence from various fields and domains.  One perspective is that success is largely determined by fate, or the predetermined course of events that is beyond human control. This view is often associated with the concept of “tian dao” (天道), or the way of heaven, in Chinese philosophy. According to this view, there is a cosmic order that governs everything in the universe, and humans must align themselves with it to achieve harmony and prosperity. Those who violate this order will face misfortune and failure. Therefore, success is not a matter of personal choice or effort, but a matter of following the natural laws and principles that are set by a higher power.  Another perspective is that success is largely determined by free will, or the ability to act according to one’s own desires and preferences. This view is often associated with the concept of “ba dao” (霸道), or the way of hegemony, in Chinese philosophy. According to this view, there is no fixed destiny or fate for anyone, and humans can shape their own future by exercising their will and power. Those who are ambitious and courageous can overcome any obstacles and challenges that they encounter, and achieve success by their own merits. Therefore, success is not a matter of external factors or luck, but a matter of personal agency and responsibility.  A third perspective is that success is a result of both fate and free will, or a combination of predetermined and contingent factors. This view acknowledges that there are some aspects of life that are beyond human control, such as genetics, environment, culture, and historical circumstances. However, it also recognizes that there are some aspects of life that are within human control, such as education, skills, habits, attitudes, and decisions. Those who are successful are able to make use of both their given advantages and their acquired abilities, and adapt to changing situations and opportunities. Therefore, success is not a matter of either-or, but a matter of both-and.  What does the evidence say about these perspectives? There is no definitive answer to this question, as different fields and domains may have different criteria and measures of success. However, some recent studies and books have suggested that luck plays a far greater role in success than most people realize. For example, researchers have found that about half of the differences in income across people worldwide is explained by their country of residence and by the income distribution within that country, that scientific impact is randomly distributed, that the chance of becoming a CEO is influenced by your name or month of birth, and that huge success in business is largely based on luck. These findings imply that success is not only a function of talent or skill, but also a function of opportunity or circumstance.  Does this mean that luck is everything? Not necessarily. Luck can be seen as a part of ability, rather than an opposite or alternative to it. Ability can be defined as the capacity to perform well in a given situation or domain. However, this capacity depends not only on one’s innate or acquired traits, but also on one’s environment or context. For example, being born with perfect pitch may be an advantage for a musician, but not for a mathematician. Similarly, being born in a wealthy country may be an advantage for an entrepreneur, but not for an artist. Therefore, ability can be seen as a function of both fit and luck. Fit refers to how well one’s traits match the demands or expectations of one’s situation or domain. Luck refers to how favorable one’s situation or domain is for one’s traits. Those who are successful are able to find or create situations or domains that fit their traits well and offer them favorable opportunities.  What about choice? Is it more important than effort? And is choice predetermined or free? These are difficult questions to answer, as they involve metaphysical and ethical issues that are beyond the scope of this essay. However, one possible way to approach them is to adopt a pragmatic perspective. According to this perspective, choice is not an abstract concept that exists independently of reality, but a concrete action that occurs in specific contexts. Choice is not something that we have or don’t have in general, but something that we do or don’t do in particular situations. Choice is not something that we can prove or disprove objectively, but something that we can evaluate or justify subjectively. Therefore, choice is not a matter of fate or free will, but a matter of pragmatism or rationality. Pragmatism refers to how well one’s choices work or succeed in one’s reality. Rationality refers to how well one’s choices are consistent or coherent with one’s values and goals. Those who are successful are able to make choices that are both pragmatic and rational, and that balance the trade-offs between effort and opportunity.  In conclusion, success is a complex and multifaceted phenomenon that depends on various factors, such as fate, free will, luck, ability, fit, choice, effort, and opportunity. There is no simple or universal formula for success, as different situations and domains may require different strategies and skills. However, some general principles that can help us achieve success are to be aware of our strengths and weaknesses, to seek or create favorable environments and contexts, to make pragmatic and rational choices, and to adapt and learn from our experiences. Success is not a fixed or predetermined outcome, but a dynamic and evolving process.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Nature of White Lies: Are They Still Lies After All?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/The-Nature-of-White-Lies-Are-They-Still-Lies-After-All/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Nature of White Lies: Are They Still Lies After All?" /><published>2023-07-25T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-25T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/The%20Nature%20of%20White%20Lies%20Are%20They%20Still%20Lies%20After%20All</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/The-Nature-of-White-Lies-Are-They-Still-Lies-After-All/">&lt;p&gt; The concept of lying, its ethical implications, and its societal impact, has been a subject of interest for philosophers, psychologists, and sociologists for centuries. The essence of lying can be defined from various angles and perspectives, often making the boundaries of its definition blurry and debatable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;defining-lies&quot;&gt;Defining Lies&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; From a simplistic perspective, a lie can be defined as a statement made by someone who knows it is not true in an attempt to deceive others. In contrast, from a socio-cultural standpoint, a lie can be seen as a breach of trust, a violation of societal norms centered around honesty and transparency. Yet, from an ethical lens, lying could be perceived as an act that compromises one’s integrity by failing to uphold the moral principle of truthfulness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;unveiling-the-white-lie&quot;&gt;Unveiling the White Lie&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; A unique category within the broad spectrum of lies is the ‘white lie’ or ‘benevolent lie’. These are untruths told out of kindness, to spare feelings, or avoid unnecessary harm. Here are three examples:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A friend who cooked a meal for the first time asks if you enjoyed it. While the food wasn’t to your liking, you compliment their effort and express gratitude, thereby encouraging them to continue learning.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A child asks if Santa Claus is real. To keep the magic of childhood alive, you affirm Santa’s existence.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A terminal patient asks about their prognosis. As a family member, to maintain their hope and spirit, you give a more optimistic response than the harsh reality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-pros-and-cons-of-white-lies&quot;&gt;The Pros and Cons of White Lies&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; White lies can be a double-edged sword. On the one hand, they can maintain harmonious relationships, protect feelings, and preserve hope. On the other hand, they can lead to the erosion of trust if discovered, potentially damaging reputations and relationships. Furthermore, they may hinder personal growth and self-improvement by shielding individuals from reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-justifiability-of-white-lies&quot;&gt;The Justifiability of White Lies&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Comparing white lies to other lies, the crucial distinction lies within the intent. While all lies are inherently untruthful, white lies are told with the aim to protect and not harm. However, the acceptability of white lies varies greatly depending on cultural, moral, and personal beliefs. Some might argue that lies, regardless of their nature, are a breach of trust, while others may perceive white lies as necessary for maintaining social harmony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;concluding-thoughts&quot;&gt;Concluding Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Should humans lie?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The answer to this question depends on one’s ethical stance. Some argue that honesty should always be upheld, while others believe that lies are occasionally necessary for the greater good.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How to lie without causing harm?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;If one must lie, it should ideally be done with the intention of minimizing harm and should not be used to exploit or manipulate others.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Are white lies truly lies?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Technically, yes, as they are false statements. However, the intent behind them sets them apart from other lies. Assessing the “goodness” of a white lie can be subjective and should be done with consideration for the context, the potential outcomes, and the individuals involved.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt; In conclusion, the concept of lying, especially white lies, is multifaceted and context-dependent. While it’s generally agreed that honesty builds trust and fosters healthy relationships, there are situations where white lies may be viewed as a lesser evil. However, it’s crucial to remember that the line between a white lie and a harmful lie can often be thin and blurred.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html"> The concept of lying, its ethical implications, and its societal impact, has been a subject of interest for philosophers, psychologists, and sociologists for centuries. The essence of lying can be defined from various angles and perspectives, often making the boundaries of its definition blurry and debatable. Defining Lies  From a simplistic perspective, a lie can be defined as a statement made by someone who knows it is not true in an attempt to deceive others. In contrast, from a socio-cultural standpoint, a lie can be seen as a breach of trust, a violation of societal norms centered around honesty and transparency. Yet, from an ethical lens, lying could be perceived as an act that compromises one’s integrity by failing to uphold the moral principle of truthfulness. Unveiling the White Lie  A unique category within the broad spectrum of lies is the ‘white lie’ or ‘benevolent lie’. These are untruths told out of kindness, to spare feelings, or avoid unnecessary harm. Here are three examples: A friend who cooked a meal for the first time asks if you enjoyed it. While the food wasn’t to your liking, you compliment their effort and express gratitude, thereby encouraging them to continue learning. A child asks if Santa Claus is real. To keep the magic of childhood alive, you affirm Santa’s existence. A terminal patient asks about their prognosis. As a family member, to maintain their hope and spirit, you give a more optimistic response than the harsh reality. The Pros and Cons of White Lies  White lies can be a double-edged sword. On the one hand, they can maintain harmonious relationships, protect feelings, and preserve hope. On the other hand, they can lead to the erosion of trust if discovered, potentially damaging reputations and relationships. Furthermore, they may hinder personal growth and self-improvement by shielding individuals from reality. The Justifiability of White Lies  Comparing white lies to other lies, the crucial distinction lies within the intent. While all lies are inherently untruthful, white lies are told with the aim to protect and not harm. However, the acceptability of white lies varies greatly depending on cultural, moral, and personal beliefs. Some might argue that lies, regardless of their nature, are a breach of trust, while others may perceive white lies as necessary for maintaining social harmony. Concluding Thoughts Should humans lie? The answer to this question depends on one’s ethical stance. Some argue that honesty should always be upheld, while others believe that lies are occasionally necessary for the greater good. How to lie without causing harm? If one must lie, it should ideally be done with the intention of minimizing harm and should not be used to exploit or manipulate others. Are white lies truly lies? Technically, yes, as they are false statements. However, the intent behind them sets them apart from other lies. Assessing the “goodness” of a white lie can be subjective and should be done with consideration for the context, the potential outcomes, and the individuals involved.  In conclusion, the concept of lying, especially white lies, is multifaceted and context-dependent. While it’s generally agreed that honesty builds trust and fosters healthy relationships, there are situations where white lies may be viewed as a lesser evil. However, it’s crucial to remember that the line between a white lie and a harmful lie can often be thin and blurred.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Is Life Worth Living?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Is-Life-Worth-Living/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Is Life Worth Living?" /><published>2023-07-24T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-24T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Is%20Life%20Worth%20Living</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Is-Life-Worth-Living/">&lt;p&gt; Is life worth living? This is a profound question that has been debated by philosophers, poets, and ordinary people throughout history. Some people may argue that life is full of suffering and hardship, and that there is little joy and happiness to be found. Others may contend that life is worth living, and that every moment can be beautiful, such as love, friendship, family, and nature. In this passage, we will examine both sides of this question and provide some examples to illustrate them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; One possible reason why some people may think that life is not worth living is that they have experienced a lot of pain and sorrow in their lives. For instance, they may have lost their loved ones, suffered from illness or injury, faced injustice or oppression, or endured poverty or war. These kinds of experiences can make people feel hopeless, depressed, angry, or bitter. They may wonder what is the meaning or purpose of their existence, and whether there is any point in continuing to live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Another possible reason why some people may think that life is not worth living is that they have a pessimistic or cynical view of the world. They may believe that the world is full of evil and suffering, and that there is no good or justice to be found. They may also think that human beings are selfish and cruel, and that they cannot trust or rely on anyone. They may feel alienated and isolated from others, and have no sense of belonging or community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; However, not everyone agrees with this negative outlook on life. Some people may think that life is worth living, and that there are many reasons to be grateful and hopeful. One possible reason why some people may think that life is worth living is that they have experienced a lot of joy and happiness in their lives. For example, they may have loved and been loved by someone, enjoyed their hobbies or passions, achieved their goals or dreams, or contributed to society or humanity. These kinds of experiences can make people feel fulfilled, satisfied, proud, or inspired. They may appreciate the value and significance of their lives, and look forward to the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Another possible reason why some people may think that life is worth living is that they have an optimistic or positive view of the world. They may believe that the world is full of beauty and wonder, and that there is always something to learn or discover. They may also think that human beings are capable of kindness and compassion, and that they can make a difference in the world. They may feel connected and involved with others, and have a sense of belonging or community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; In conclusion, whether life is worth living or not depends on one’s perspective and attitude. Some people may focus on the negative aspects of life and lose hope and meaning. Others may focus on the positive aspects of life and find hope and meaning. Ultimately, it is up to each individual to decide how they want to live their lives, and what makes them happy or unhappy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;qs&quot;&gt;QS:&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is the main question that the passage explores?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What are two possible reasons why some people may think that life is not worth living, according to the passage?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What are two possible reasons why some people may think that life is worth living, according to the passage?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is the conclusion of the passage?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html"> Is life worth living? This is a profound question that has been debated by philosophers, poets, and ordinary people throughout history. Some people may argue that life is full of suffering and hardship, and that there is little joy and happiness to be found. Others may contend that life is worth living, and that every moment can be beautiful, such as love, friendship, family, and nature. In this passage, we will examine both sides of this question and provide some examples to illustrate them.  One possible reason why some people may think that life is not worth living is that they have experienced a lot of pain and sorrow in their lives. For instance, they may have lost their loved ones, suffered from illness or injury, faced injustice or oppression, or endured poverty or war. These kinds of experiences can make people feel hopeless, depressed, angry, or bitter. They may wonder what is the meaning or purpose of their existence, and whether there is any point in continuing to live.  Another possible reason why some people may think that life is not worth living is that they have a pessimistic or cynical view of the world. They may believe that the world is full of evil and suffering, and that there is no good or justice to be found. They may also think that human beings are selfish and cruel, and that they cannot trust or rely on anyone. They may feel alienated and isolated from others, and have no sense of belonging or community.  However, not everyone agrees with this negative outlook on life. Some people may think that life is worth living, and that there are many reasons to be grateful and hopeful. One possible reason why some people may think that life is worth living is that they have experienced a lot of joy and happiness in their lives. For example, they may have loved and been loved by someone, enjoyed their hobbies or passions, achieved their goals or dreams, or contributed to society or humanity. These kinds of experiences can make people feel fulfilled, satisfied, proud, or inspired. They may appreciate the value and significance of their lives, and look forward to the future.  Another possible reason why some people may think that life is worth living is that they have an optimistic or positive view of the world. They may believe that the world is full of beauty and wonder, and that there is always something to learn or discover. They may also think that human beings are capable of kindness and compassion, and that they can make a difference in the world. They may feel connected and involved with others, and have a sense of belonging or community.  In conclusion, whether life is worth living or not depends on one’s perspective and attitude. Some people may focus on the negative aspects of life and lose hope and meaning. Others may focus on the positive aspects of life and find hope and meaning. Ultimately, it is up to each individual to decide how they want to live their lives, and what makes them happy or unhappy.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Nature of Human Morality</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/The-Nature-of-Human-Morality/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Nature of Human Morality" /><published>2023-07-23T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-23T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/The%20Nature%20of%20Human%20Morality</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/The-Nature-of-Human-Morality/">&lt;p&gt; Human nature is a perennial topic of debate among philosophers, psychologists, biologists, and other disciplines. Are humans inherently good or evil? Do they have an innate sense of morality or are they shaped by their environment and culture? How do genes, brain, and behavior interact to influence moral judgments and actions? These are some of the questions that have fascinated and perplexed scholars and laypeople alike for centuries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; One way to approach this topic is to examine the evolutionary origins of morality. Some researchers have argued that humans are moral beings by nature because their biological makeup determines the presence of three necessary conditions for ethical behavior: the ability to anticipate the consequences of one’s own actions, the ability to make value judgments, and the ability to choose between alternative courses of action. Morality consists of the urge or predisposition to judge human actions as either right or wrong in terms of their consequences for other human beings. Moreover, some studies have suggested that morality is not unique to humans, but can be traced to the behaviors of many other social animals, such as chimpanzees, elephants, dolphins, and rats. These animals have been observed to exhibit empathy, altruism, cooperation, fairness, and justice in various situations. For example, rats will free a trapped companion even if it means giving up a reward. These findings imply that morality has a biological basis and is influenced by natural selection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Another way to explore this topic is to investigate the psychological and neural mechanisms of moral reasoning. Some researchers have proposed that morality is based on two distinct processes: intuition and reflection. Intuition is often automatic and effortless, leading to actions that occur without insight into the reasons behind them. Reflection, on the other hand, is all about conscious thought - identifying possible behaviors, weighing the costs and benefits of likely outcomes, and rationally deciding on a course of action. Depending on the situation, people may rely more on one process than the other. For example, in the classic trolley dilemma, most people would intuitively throw a switch to divert a runaway trolley away from five people and onto one person, but they would hesitate to push a man off a bridge to achieve the same outcome. This suggests that different moral judgments are triggered by different emotional responses. Furthermore, some researchers have identified specific brain regions involved in moral cognition, such as the prefrontal cortex, the temporoparietal junction, and the amygdala. These regions are responsible for functions such as theory of mind (the ability to infer others’ mental states), empathy (the ability to share others’ emotions), and emotion regulation (the ability to control one’s own emotions). By using techniques such as functional magnetic resonance imaging (fMRI) and lesion studies, these researchers have shown how brain damage or stimulation can affect moral judgments and behaviors. For instance, patients with damage to the ventromedial prefrontal cortex tend to make more utilitarian decisions in moral dilemmas than healthy controls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; A third way to approach this topic is to consider the social and cultural influences on morality. Some researchers have argued that morality is not fixed or universal, but relative and variable across time and space. They contend that moral values are shaped by social norms, traditions, religions, laws, and institutions that vary from one society to another. They also point out that moral judgments are often influenced by factors such as group identity, authority, conformity, obedience, and bias. For example, people may judge an action as morally right or wrong depending on whether it was performed by an ingroup or an outgroup member. They may also follow or disobey a moral rule depending on whether it was imposed by a legitimate or illegitimate authority figure. These findings imply that morality is a social construct and is influenced by social learning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; In conclusion, human nature is a complex and multifaceted phenomenon that cannot be reduced to a simple dichotomy of good or evil. Rather, it is the result of an interplay between biological, psychological, social, and cultural factors that shape moral judgments and actions in different ways. Therefore, instead of asking whether humans are good or evil by nature, it may be more fruitful to ask how humans can become more moral in practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;qs&quot;&gt;QS:&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;According to the article, what are the three necessary conditions for ethical behavior? (Choose three)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A) The ability to anticipate the consequences of one’s own actions&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;B) The ability to make value judgments&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;C) The ability to choose between alternative courses of action&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;D) The ability to empathize with others’ emotions&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;E) The ability to follow social norms and laws&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;According to the article, what is the difference between intuition and reflection in moral reasoning? (Choose one)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A) Intuition is based on emotional responses, while reflection is based on rational decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;B) Intuition is based on biological factors, while reflection is based on cultural factors.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;C) Intuition is based on universal principles, while reflection is based on relative values.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;D) Intuition is based on individual preferences, while reflection is based on group interests.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;According to the article, what are some of the social and cultural influences on morality? (Choose two)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A) Group identity&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;B) Natural selection&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;C) Brain regions&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;D) Authority&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;E) Moral dilemmas&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html"> Human nature is a perennial topic of debate among philosophers, psychologists, biologists, and other disciplines. Are humans inherently good or evil? Do they have an innate sense of morality or are they shaped by their environment and culture? How do genes, brain, and behavior interact to influence moral judgments and actions? These are some of the questions that have fascinated and perplexed scholars and laypeople alike for centuries.  One way to approach this topic is to examine the evolutionary origins of morality. Some researchers have argued that humans are moral beings by nature because their biological makeup determines the presence of three necessary conditions for ethical behavior: the ability to anticipate the consequences of one’s own actions, the ability to make value judgments, and the ability to choose between alternative courses of action. Morality consists of the urge or predisposition to judge human actions as either right or wrong in terms of their consequences for other human beings. Moreover, some studies have suggested that morality is not unique to humans, but can be traced to the behaviors of many other social animals, such as chimpanzees, elephants, dolphins, and rats. These animals have been observed to exhibit empathy, altruism, cooperation, fairness, and justice in various situations. For example, rats will free a trapped companion even if it means giving up a reward. These findings imply that morality has a biological basis and is influenced by natural selection.  Another way to explore this topic is to investigate the psychological and neural mechanisms of moral reasoning. Some researchers have proposed that morality is based on two distinct processes: intuition and reflection. Intuition is often automatic and effortless, leading to actions that occur without insight into the reasons behind them. Reflection, on the other hand, is all about conscious thought - identifying possible behaviors, weighing the costs and benefits of likely outcomes, and rationally deciding on a course of action. Depending on the situation, people may rely more on one process than the other. For example, in the classic trolley dilemma, most people would intuitively throw a switch to divert a runaway trolley away from five people and onto one person, but they would hesitate to push a man off a bridge to achieve the same outcome. This suggests that different moral judgments are triggered by different emotional responses. Furthermore, some researchers have identified specific brain regions involved in moral cognition, such as the prefrontal cortex, the temporoparietal junction, and the amygdala. These regions are responsible for functions such as theory of mind (the ability to infer others’ mental states), empathy (the ability to share others’ emotions), and emotion regulation (the ability to control one’s own emotions). By using techniques such as functional magnetic resonance imaging (fMRI) and lesion studies, these researchers have shown how brain damage or stimulation can affect moral judgments and behaviors. For instance, patients with damage to the ventromedial prefrontal cortex tend to make more utilitarian decisions in moral dilemmas than healthy controls.  A third way to approach this topic is to consider the social and cultural influences on morality. Some researchers have argued that morality is not fixed or universal, but relative and variable across time and space. They contend that moral values are shaped by social norms, traditions, religions, laws, and institutions that vary from one society to another. They also point out that moral judgments are often influenced by factors such as group identity, authority, conformity, obedience, and bias. For example, people may judge an action as morally right or wrong depending on whether it was performed by an ingroup or an outgroup member. They may also follow or disobey a moral rule depending on whether it was imposed by a legitimate or illegitimate authority figure. These findings imply that morality is a social construct and is influenced by social learning.  In conclusion, human nature is a complex and multifaceted phenomenon that cannot be reduced to a simple dichotomy of good or evil. Rather, it is the result of an interplay between biological, psychological, social, and cultural factors that shape moral judgments and actions in different ways. Therefore, instead of asking whether humans are good or evil by nature, it may be more fruitful to ask how humans can become more moral in practice.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Is justice delayed justice?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Is-justice-delayed-justice/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Is justice delayed justice?" /><published>2023-07-22T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-22T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Is%20justice%20delayed%20justice</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Is-justice-delayed-justice/">&lt;p&gt; Justice is a concept that refers to the fair and impartial treatment of people according to the rules of law and morality. Justice is often seen as a fundamental value and a human right that everyone deserves. However, justice is not always easy to achieve or maintain, especially in a world where there are conflicts, inequalities, and injustices. Sometimes, justice can be delayed or denied for various reasons, such as corruption, discrimination, violence, or bureaucracy. When this happens, people may suffer from harm, loss, or oppression that are not properly addressed or compensated. The question then arises: Is justice delayed justice? Or, in other words, does justice lose its meaning or value when it is not timely or effective?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; There are different ways to approach this question, depending on one’s perspective and criteria. Some people may argue that justice delayed is still justice, as long as it eventually arrives and restores the balance and order that were disrupted by injustice. They may point out that justice is not only about the outcome, but also about the process and the intention. As long as the process is fair and transparent, and the intention is sincere and genuine, justice can still be served even if it takes time. They may also emphasize that justice is not absolute or perfect, but relative and pragmatic. Sometimes, justice has to be balanced with other factors, such as peace, stability, or forgiveness. Therefore, justice delayed may be a necessary compromise or sacrifice for a greater good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; On the other hand, some people may argue that justice delayed is justice denied, as it fails to provide adequate and timely relief or remedy to the victims of injustice. They may point out that justice is not only about the process and the intention, but also about the impact and the consequence. If the impact is severe and irreversible, and the consequence is lasting and detrimental, justice delayed may not be able to undo or repair the damage that has been done. They may also emphasize that justice is not relative or pragmatic, but absolute and ideal. Sometimes, justice has to be prioritized over other factors, such as peace, stability, or forgiveness. Therefore, justice delayed may be an unacceptable violation or betrayal of a fundamental value or right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Another way to approach this question is to consider the different types and levels of justice that exist in society. For example, there are criminal justice, civil justice, social justice, and environmental justice, among others. Each type of justice has its own goals, standards, and mechanisms, and each level of justice operates at different scales, such as local, national, or global. Depending on the type and level of justice involved, the meaning and value of timeliness and effectiveness may vary. For instance, criminal justice may require more urgency and accuracy than civil justice, because it deals with more serious crimes and punishments. Similarly, global justice may require more patience and flexibility than local justice, because it involves more diverse actors and interests. Therefore, justice delayed may have different implications and outcomes for different types of and levels of justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Summary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; The question of whether justice delayed is justice is a complex and controversial one that has no definitive answer. It depends on one’s perspective and criteria, as well as on the type and level of justice involved. Some people may see justice delayed as still justice, while others may see it as justice denied. Some people may see justice delayed as a necessary compromise or sacrifice for a greater good, while others may see it as an unacceptable violation or betrayal of a fundamental value or right. Some people may see justice delayed as having different implications and outcomes for different types of and levels of justice, while others may see it as having a universal impact and consequence for all types of and levels of justice.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html"> Justice is a concept that refers to the fair and impartial treatment of people according to the rules of law and morality. Justice is often seen as a fundamental value and a human right that everyone deserves. However, justice is not always easy to achieve or maintain, especially in a world where there are conflicts, inequalities, and injustices. Sometimes, justice can be delayed or denied for various reasons, such as corruption, discrimination, violence, or bureaucracy. When this happens, people may suffer from harm, loss, or oppression that are not properly addressed or compensated. The question then arises: Is justice delayed justice? Or, in other words, does justice lose its meaning or value when it is not timely or effective?  There are different ways to approach this question, depending on one’s perspective and criteria. Some people may argue that justice delayed is still justice, as long as it eventually arrives and restores the balance and order that were disrupted by injustice. They may point out that justice is not only about the outcome, but also about the process and the intention. As long as the process is fair and transparent, and the intention is sincere and genuine, justice can still be served even if it takes time. They may also emphasize that justice is not absolute or perfect, but relative and pragmatic. Sometimes, justice has to be balanced with other factors, such as peace, stability, or forgiveness. Therefore, justice delayed may be a necessary compromise or sacrifice for a greater good.  On the other hand, some people may argue that justice delayed is justice denied, as it fails to provide adequate and timely relief or remedy to the victims of injustice. They may point out that justice is not only about the process and the intention, but also about the impact and the consequence. If the impact is severe and irreversible, and the consequence is lasting and detrimental, justice delayed may not be able to undo or repair the damage that has been done. They may also emphasize that justice is not relative or pragmatic, but absolute and ideal. Sometimes, justice has to be prioritized over other factors, such as peace, stability, or forgiveness. Therefore, justice delayed may be an unacceptable violation or betrayal of a fundamental value or right.  Another way to approach this question is to consider the different types and levels of justice that exist in society. For example, there are criminal justice, civil justice, social justice, and environmental justice, among others. Each type of justice has its own goals, standards, and mechanisms, and each level of justice operates at different scales, such as local, national, or global. Depending on the type and level of justice involved, the meaning and value of timeliness and effectiveness may vary. For instance, criminal justice may require more urgency and accuracy than civil justice, because it deals with more serious crimes and punishments. Similarly, global justice may require more patience and flexibility than local justice, because it involves more diverse actors and interests. Therefore, justice delayed may have different implications and outcomes for different types of and levels of justice. Summary  The question of whether justice delayed is justice is a complex and controversial one that has no definitive answer. It depends on one’s perspective and criteria, as well as on the type and level of justice involved. Some people may see justice delayed as still justice, while others may see it as justice denied. Some people may see justice delayed as a necessary compromise or sacrifice for a greater good, while others may see it as an unacceptable violation or betrayal of a fundamental value or right. Some people may see justice delayed as having different implications and outcomes for different types of and levels of justice, while others may see it as having a universal impact and consequence for all types of and levels of justice.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Is the ending of a story important?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Is-the-ending-of-a-story-important/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Is the ending of a story important?" /><published>2023-07-21T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-21T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Is%20the%20ending%20of%20a%20story%20important</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Is-the-ending-of-a-story-important/">&lt;p&gt; A story is a form of communication that conveys a message, a theme, or a moral to the audience. A story can be told in various ways, such as through books, movies, plays, songs, or games. A story usually consists of three main parts: the beginning, the middle, and the end. The beginning introduces the characters, the setting, and the conflict; the middle develops the plot, the suspense, and the character arcs; and the end resolves the conflict, answers the questions, and concludes the theme. But is the ending of a story more important than the other parts? How does the ending affect the overall impact and meaning of a story? What are some of the factors that make a good or bad ending? These are some of the questions that we will explore in this essay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; The ending of a story matters because it is the final impression that the audience will have of the story. The ending shows the audience what to feel, what to learn, and what to remember from the story. The ending also reveals the purpose and intention of the storyteller. A good ending will leave the audience feeling satisfied, enlightened, and inspired. A bad ending will leave them feeling disappointed, confused, and frustrated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; There are different types of endings that can be used in stories, depending on the genre, tone, and message of the story. Some of the common types are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Happy endings: These are endings where the protagonist achieves their goal, overcomes their obstacle, or defeats their enemy. The audience feels happy for them and shares their joy. Happy endings are often used in genres such as romance, comedy, or adventure.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sad endings: These are endings where the protagonist fails to achieve their goal, succumbs to their obstacle, or loses to their enemy. The audience feels sad for them and empathizes with their pain. Sad endings are often used in genres such as tragedy, drama, or horror.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ambiguous endings: These are endings where the outcome is unclear or open to interpretation. The audience is left wondering what happened or what will happen next. Ambiguous endings are often used in genres such as mystery, thriller, or science fiction.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Twist endings: These are endings where something unexpected or surprising happens that changes the perspective or meaning of the story. The audience is shocked or amazed by the revelation or reversal. Twist endings are often used in genres such as crime, fantasy, or psychological.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Regardless of what type of ending a story has, there are some factors that make an ending good or bad. Some of these factors are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Consistency: A good ending should be consistent with the rest of the story in terms of plot, character, tone, and theme. It should not contradict or ignore what has been established before. It should also not introduce new elements or information that have not been foreshadowed or explained earlier.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Clarity: A good ending should be clear and understandable to the audience. It should not be confusing or vague to the point where the audience does not know what happened or why it happened. It should also not be too predictable or obvious to the point where the audience feels bored or cheated.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Closure: A good ending should provide closure to the main conflict and questions of the story. It should not leave too many loose ends or unresolved issues that make the audience feel unsatisfied or frustrated. It should also not wrap up everything too neatly or conveniently that make the audience feel manipulated or unrealistic.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Creativity: A good ending should be creative and original to the audience. It should not be clichéd or stereotypical to the point where the audience feels disappointed or indifferent. It should also not be random or illogical to the point where the audience feels annoyed or insulted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Summary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; The ending of a story is important because it determines how the audience will remember and evaluate the story. A good ending will enhance the impact and meaning of the story, while a bad ending will diminish them. There are different types of endings that can be used in stories, depending on the genre, tone, and message of the story. There are also different factors that make an ending good or bad, such as consistency, clarity, closure, and creativity. Knowing how to write a good ending is one of the most essential skills for a storyteller.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html"> A story is a form of communication that conveys a message, a theme, or a moral to the audience. A story can be told in various ways, such as through books, movies, plays, songs, or games. A story usually consists of three main parts: the beginning, the middle, and the end. The beginning introduces the characters, the setting, and the conflict; the middle develops the plot, the suspense, and the character arcs; and the end resolves the conflict, answers the questions, and concludes the theme. But is the ending of a story more important than the other parts? How does the ending affect the overall impact and meaning of a story? What are some of the factors that make a good or bad ending? These are some of the questions that we will explore in this essay.  The ending of a story matters because it is the final impression that the audience will have of the story. The ending shows the audience what to feel, what to learn, and what to remember from the story. The ending also reveals the purpose and intention of the storyteller. A good ending will leave the audience feeling satisfied, enlightened, and inspired. A bad ending will leave them feeling disappointed, confused, and frustrated.  There are different types of endings that can be used in stories, depending on the genre, tone, and message of the story. Some of the common types are: Happy endings: These are endings where the protagonist achieves their goal, overcomes their obstacle, or defeats their enemy. The audience feels happy for them and shares their joy. Happy endings are often used in genres such as romance, comedy, or adventure. Sad endings: These are endings where the protagonist fails to achieve their goal, succumbs to their obstacle, or loses to their enemy. The audience feels sad for them and empathizes with their pain. Sad endings are often used in genres such as tragedy, drama, or horror. Ambiguous endings: These are endings where the outcome is unclear or open to interpretation. The audience is left wondering what happened or what will happen next. Ambiguous endings are often used in genres such as mystery, thriller, or science fiction. Twist endings: These are endings where something unexpected or surprising happens that changes the perspective or meaning of the story. The audience is shocked or amazed by the revelation or reversal. Twist endings are often used in genres such as crime, fantasy, or psychological.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Art of Chasing Dreams</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/The-Art-of-Chasing-Dreams/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Art of Chasing Dreams" /><published>2023-07-20T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2023-07-20T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/The-Art-of-Chasing-Dreams</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/The-Art-of-Chasing-Dreams/">&lt;p&gt; How should we chase our dreams in a fast-paced world? This is a question that troubles many people. Today’s Chinese society is a very fast-paced era, where the subway is crowded with people at six or seven in the morning. High school students get up at five or six o’clock, study hard, finish their evening classes at around eleven o’clock, and then wash and sleep, with insufficient sleep time. Workers work 996, and overtime is normal. Under the fierce social competition, this also brings many negative impacts. For example, people’s physical and mental health are devastated, the decline in fertility rate has a long-term impact on society, and aging is becoming more and more serious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; But people always have to have dreams. In such a cruel world, how should we have dreams and pursue and achieve them? This is not a simple question, nor is there a standard answer. Everyone has their own dreams and their own ways to achieve them. However, we can explore the art of chasing dreams from the following aspects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;define-your-dreams&quot;&gt;Define your dreams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; First of all, we need to be clear about what our dreams are. Dreams are an abstract and concrete concept. They can be a lofty and difficult goal, such as becoming an astronaut or a Nobel Prize winner; or they can be a simple and practical wish, such as traveling the world or having a house that you like. No matter what kind of dream, we need to know clearly what it is, why we want it, and what it means to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Defining dreams is not easy, because we may be influenced and disturbed by external factors, such as family, society, media, etc. Sometimes we may mistake other people’s dreams for our own, or be bound by what others expect and require of us. Therefore, we need to spend time and energy to explore what we really want deep in our hearts and express it bravely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;plan-your-dreams&quot;&gt;Plan your dreams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Secondly, we need to make a reasonable and effective plan to achieve our dreams. A plan is a bridge that turns dreams into reality. It can help us clarify what we need to do, how to do it, and when to do it. A plan can also give us more motivation and confidence to chase our dreams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Making a plan is not difficult, but executing a plan is very difficult. Because in the process of chasing dreams, we may encounter various difficulties and challenges, such as time, money, resources, skills, competition, pressure, etc. These difficulties and challenges may make us feel frustrated, disappointed, exhausted or give up. Therefore, we need to have a flexible and persistent attitude to adjust our plan according to different situations and changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;enjoy-your-dreams&quot;&gt;Enjoy your dreams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Finally, we need to learn to enjoy the process of chasing our dreams. Dreams are a beautiful and distant goal that may require us to pay a lot of effort and sacrifice, and sometimes we may not be able to reach them. But this does not mean that we cannot get happiness and satisfaction from them. Because chasing dreams itself is an experience of growth and progress that can make us discover our potential and value, as well as make us meet new friends and partners, and gain new knowledge and skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Enjoying chasing dreams is not easy because we may be troubled by the standards and expectations set by ourselves or others, such as scores, grades, rankings, evaluations etc. These standards and expectations may make us ignore our efforts and progress, and also make us forget our original intention and fun. Therefore, we need to have a positive and grateful attitude to appreciate every step we take, and also have an open and curious attitude to explore every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Chasing dreams is an art that requires us to have clear definitions, reasonable plans, and pleasant enjoyment. How should we chase our dreams in a fast-paced world? This is a question worth thinking about and practicing. Because only when we have and chase our own dreams, can we truly live out our wonderfulness and meaning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;qs&quot;&gt;QS:&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is the main topic of the passage?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A) How to find your dreams in a fast-paced world&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;B) How to chase your dreams in a fast-paced world&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;C) How to enjoy your dreams in a fast-paced world&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;D) How to define your dreams in a fast-paced world&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What are the three aspects that the author explores to discuss the art of chasing dreams?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A) Define, plan, and enjoy&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;B) Dream, act, and achieve&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;C) Discover, create, and share&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;D) Imagine, design, and execute&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What are some of the difficulties and challenges that people may encounter in the process of chasing dreams, according to the passage?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A) Time, money, resources, skills, competition, pressure&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;B) Family, society, media, expectations, standards, evaluations&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;C) Health, fertility, aging, environment, education, employment&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;D) All of the above&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What are some of the benefits and rewards that people can get from chasing dreams, according to the passage?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A) Growth, progress, potential, value&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;B) Friends, partners, knowledge, skills&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;C) Happiness, satisfaction, wonderfulness, meaning&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;D) All of the above&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What are some of the attitudes that people need to have to chase their dreams effectively and pleasantly, according to the passage?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A) Brave, flexible, persistent&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;B) Positive, grateful, appreciative&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;C) Open, curious, exploratory&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;D) All of the above&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Super Aring</name></author><summary type="html"> How should we chase our dreams in a fast-paced world? This is a question that troubles many people. Today’s Chinese society is a very fast-paced era, where the subway is crowded with people at six or seven in the morning. High school students get up at five or six o’clock, study hard, finish their evening classes at around eleven o’clock, and then wash and sleep, with insufficient sleep time. Workers work 996, and overtime is normal. Under the fierce social competition, this also brings many negative impacts. For example, people’s physical and mental health are devastated, the decline in fertility rate has a long-term impact on society, and aging is becoming more and more serious.  But people always have to have dreams. In such a cruel world, how should we have dreams and pursue and achieve them? This is not a simple question, nor is there a standard answer. Everyone has their own dreams and their own ways to achieve them. However, we can explore the art of chasing dreams from the following aspects. Define your dreams  First of all, we need to be clear about what our dreams are. Dreams are an abstract and concrete concept. They can be a lofty and difficult goal, such as becoming an astronaut or a Nobel Prize winner; or they can be a simple and practical wish, such as traveling the world or having a house that you like. No matter what kind of dream, we need to know clearly what it is, why we want it, and what it means to us.  Defining dreams is not easy, because we may be influenced and disturbed by external factors, such as family, society, media, etc. Sometimes we may mistake other people’s dreams for our own, or be bound by what others expect and require of us. Therefore, we need to spend time and energy to explore what we really want deep in our hearts and express it bravely. Plan your dreams  Secondly, we need to make a reasonable and effective plan to achieve our dreams. A plan is a bridge that turns dreams into reality. It can help us clarify what we need to do, how to do it, and when to do it. A plan can also give us more motivation and confidence to chase our dreams.  Making a plan is not difficult, but executing a plan is very difficult. Because in the process of chasing dreams, we may encounter various difficulties and challenges, such as time, money, resources, skills, competition, pressure, etc. These difficulties and challenges may make us feel frustrated, disappointed, exhausted or give up. Therefore, we need to have a flexible and persistent attitude to adjust our plan according to different situations and changes. Enjoy your dreams  Finally, we need to learn to enjoy the process of chasing our dreams. Dreams are a beautiful and distant goal that may require us to pay a lot of effort and sacrifice, and sometimes we may not be able to reach them. But this does not mean that we cannot get happiness and satisfaction from them. Because chasing dreams itself is an experience of growth and progress that can make us discover our potential and value, as well as make us meet new friends and partners, and gain new knowledge and skills.  Enjoying chasing dreams is not easy because we may be troubled by the standards and expectations set by ourselves or others, such as scores, grades, rankings, evaluations etc. These standards and expectations may make us ignore our efforts and progress, and also make us forget our original intention and fun. Therefore, we need to have a positive and grateful attitude to appreciate every step we take, and also have an open and curious attitude to explore every day. Summary  Chasing dreams is an art that requires us to have clear definitions, reasonable plans, and pleasant enjoyment. How should we chase our dreams in a fast-paced world? This is a question worth thinking about and practicing. Because only when we have and chase our own dreams, can we truly live out our wonderfulness and meaning.</summary></entry></feed>